<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Very Good Garage</title><link>https://garage.gg/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Very Good Garage</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://garage.gg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://garage.gg/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garage.gg/about/</guid><description>Look at us!</description></item><item><title>Careers</title><link>https://garage.gg/careers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garage.gg/careers/</guid><description>Because we&amp;rsquo;re such a small YouTube channel, we don&amp;rsquo;t yet have enough revenue to support a position here at Very Good Garage, but we&amp;rsquo;d love to in the future!
Check back here later or email us at help@garage.gg if you&amp;rsquo;d like us to let you know when a position becomes available for something.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://garage.gg/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garage.gg/contact/</guid><description>If you have any questions, problems with an order, inquiries about advertising with us, etc, please contact us at help@garage.gg and we will be sure to get back to you as quickly as possible!</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://garage.gg/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garage.gg/privacy/</guid><description>PRIVACY NOTICE
Last updated February 21, 2021
Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at Very good Garage LLC, doing business as Very Good Garage (&amp;ldquo;Very Good Garage&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at help@garage.</description></item><item><title>Returns</title><link>https://garage.gg/returns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garage.gg/returns/</guid><description>Very Good Garage aims to provide a happy shopping experience for all of our customers, but we do understand that sometimes a product is just not right for you. We aim to make our returns and exchanges program as simple as possible for our valued customers.
Within 30 days You must contact our support team about any issues with your order within 30 days of delivery
Includes original packaging &amp;amp; product in like-new condition Any returned product(s) must be returned with any original packaging, and in the condition which the product(s) arrived.</description></item><item><title>Shipping</title><link>https://garage.gg/shipping/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garage.gg/shipping/</guid><description>Very Good Garage offers shipping wherever USPS will ship to.
USA &amp;amp; Canada Orders Most deliveries within the US &amp;amp; Canada should arrive within 7 days after your shipping confirmation email is received.
Worldwide Orders Deliveries outside of the US &amp;amp; Canada may take anywhere from 7-30 days to arrive, depending on the destination country.
These times may be delayed by a number of factors, including delays in customs processing within your destination country.</description></item><item><title>Something went wrong!</title><link>https://garage.gg/error/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garage.gg/error/</guid><description> If you think this is a mistake, please contact us at help@garage.gg. Otherwise, please enjoy this picture of the 'Burb on another tow truck.</description></item><item><title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title><link>https://garage.gg/terms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garage.gg/terms/</guid><description>AGREEMENT TO TERMS These Terms of Use constitute a legally binding agreement made between you, whether personally or on behalf of an entity (&amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo;) and Very Good Garage (&amp;ldquo;Company&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;), concerning your access to and use of the Very good Garage website as well as any other media form, media channel, mobile website or mobile application related, linked, or otherwise connected thereto (collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;). You agree that by accessing the Site, you have read, understood, and agreed to be bound by all of these Terms of Use.</description></item></channel></rss>